Guide to the History of Education Society collection, 1960-2013 MS2341
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Governance and Society records, 1960-2006; Series 2
  - Correspondence between Donna Hulsizer and Michael B. Katz, June 1979; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence between Dorothy Ross and Dr. Berson 1980, October 8, 1980; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence from Dorothy Ross to Robin Berson, 1977, 1985; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence between Douglas R. Skopp and Ms. Berson, July 23, 1979; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence between Douglas Sloan and Charles Debenedetti, March 3, 1983; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence between Douglas Sloan, Howard Mehlinger and Edward McClellan, February 20, 1985; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence from Douglas Sloan to Jennings Wagoner, 1985; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence between Douglas Sloan, Jennings Wagoner, and David Ment, April 16, 1985; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence Between Douglas Sloan and Members, December 12, 1983; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence between Douglas Sloan and Professor Marvin Lazerson, May 9, 1983; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence between Douglas Sloan and Professor Mattingly, June 24, 1983; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence between Douglas Sloan and Sol Cohen, June 24, 1983; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence between Douglas Sloan and Sol Cohen, August 3, 1982; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between Dr. Geraldine Joncich Clifford and June Armstrong, November 7, 1977; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence between Dr. J.A. Mangan and Joan Burstyn, undated; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence between Dr. Lanier and Joan Burstyn, June 12, 1985; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence Between Dr. Marvin Lazerson and John Calam, December 27, 1983; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence between Dr. Philip Rulon and Editor of the History of Education Quarterly, February 14, 1969; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence between Dr. Wayne J. Urban and Robert R. Sherman, April 24, 1980; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence between Dr. William Reese and Jennings Wagoner, November 1984; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence between Earl Beck and Henry Perkinson, July 29, 1967; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence to Editor, January 7, 1987; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence between Edward McClellan and Geraldine J. Clifford, June 29, 1977; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence between Edward Nussel, Charles Sprandel, Allen Repashy and Henry Perkinson, December 26, 1967; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence between Edward R. Beauchamp and Carl Kaestle, February 4, 1981; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence between Eileen Kane and Ms. Mary Jane Edelberg, February 27, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence between Eileen Kane and Professor Geraldine Clifford, July 28, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Condliffe Lagemann and Paul Mattingly, October 19, 1982; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and B. Edward McClellan, July 14, 1988; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and Barbara Finkelstein, October 20, 1987; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and David Adams, July 25, 1988; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and Donald Warren, September 19, 1988; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and H.E.S. Board of Directors, December 14, 1987; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and Howard Mehlinger, November 30, 1987; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and J. Harrison Means, June 15, 1988; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and J. Harrison Means, July 25, 1988; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and Jeffrey Mirel, October 20, 1987; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and John Harris, July 25, 1988; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and Lynn Gordon, September 19, 1988; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and Maxine Seller, September 19, 1988; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and Peggy Elliott, November 30, 1987; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and Richard Attenbaugh, October 13, 1987; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and Robert Church, September 19, 1988; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence between ellen Lagemann and Ronald Cohen, July 14, 1988; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and Wayne Urban, October 20, 1987; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence between Ellen Lagemann and William Reese, July 14, 1988; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence: Ellen Schrecker, October 11, 1987; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence between Erwin Goldenstein and Henry Perkinson, December 19, 1969; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Acquisitions Departments, March 16, 1967; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence between F. Michael Perko and hsi Colleagues of the H.E.S., September 5, 1984; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence between F. Michael Perko and Mr. Robin Berson, January 13, 1982; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence between Fernandez-Perez and History of Education Quarterly, 1980; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence between Franklin E. Court and Professor McLachlan 1985, May 12, 1985; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence between Francis Paul Prucha and Professor Clifford, April 19, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence between Frederick E. Dalzillo and Paul H. Mattingly, April 7, 1975; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence between Frederick E. Salzillo and Paul H. Mattingly, November 26, 1974; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence between Fritz K. Ringer and Boston University, June 27, 1978; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence between Gene Glass and Principals in the AERA 1970 Graduate Student Seminar Program, November 20, 1969; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence between Gentle People and Robin Berson, January 1981; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence between Gerald Cannon and Paul Mattingly, October 26, 1972; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence between Gerald Gutek and Wayne J. Urban, June 30, 1980; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence between Gerald L. Soliday and Professor Berson 1984, March 23, 1984; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence between Gerald L. Gutek and Henry Perkinson 1969, November 13, 1969; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine Clifford and Sol Cohen, October 29, 1980; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine Joncich Clifford, February 24, 1977; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine Joncich Clifford and All the Participants in the 1976 Annual Meeting, August 23, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Dean Mary Constance Lynn, June 3, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine Joncich Clifford and Department of History, February 6, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Dr. David M. Ment, November 6, 1984; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Dr. Gibson, February 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Dr. Persis C. Hunt, June 25, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Dr. Susanna Hayes, March 23, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Mrs. Janet James, June 18, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Mr. Singer, March 21, 1977; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine Joncich Clifford and Patricia A. Graham, January 30, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Patricia Foster Haines, July 16, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Paul Mattingly, April 30, 1975; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine Joncich and Professor Axtell, February 5, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Professor Edward McClellan, 1977; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence between Eileen Kane and Professor Charles Burgess, July 20, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Professor Christopher J. Lucas, November 29, 1978; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine Joncich Clifford and Professor David Madsen, January 3, 1974; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine Joncich Clifford and Professor Elbert, July 15, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Professor Elbert, March 10, 1977; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Professor Jurgen Herbst, November 7, 1978; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine Joncich Clifford and Professor Neal Salisbury, February 6, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Professor Paul Mattingly, January 30, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine Joncich and Professor Persis Hunt, February 4, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Professor Robert McCaughey, March 25, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Professor Robert W. Mardock, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Professor Ronald K. Goodenow, June 2, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine Joncich and Professor Singer, February 25, 1977; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine Joncich Clifford and Professor Stephen J. Knitz, February 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Professor Story, May 5, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Professor Vincent P. Lannie, March 10, 1975; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence between Geraldine J. Clifford and Studies in the Education Elites, 1976; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence between Geoffrey J. Giles and Dr. Berson 1984, April 3, 1984; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence between Giovanni Genovisi and Participants of the 8th International Standing Conference for the History of Education, September 1986; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence between Harris Dew and Peter Swords, David Ment, 1989; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence between Harvey J. Graff and Paul and Robin, April 21, 1981; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence between Helen Horowitz and Paul Mattingly, 1970-1974; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence between Henry D. Smith and Paul H. Mattingly, October 14, 1973; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Paul Nash, May 1, 1967; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and Allen Carpenter, August 1970; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Anne Keppel 1966, March- April 1966; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Wilson Smith, June 30, 1966; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Paul Nash, February 28, 1966; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 112)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Wilson Smith, March 8, 1966; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 113)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Wilson Smith 1966, March 8, 1966; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 114)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and the Board of the History of Education, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 115)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and William E. Burgess, September 1969; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and Calvin Gower, August 1969; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 117)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Dean Morey R. Fields 1966, January 17, 1966; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 118)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Ann Keppel, May 10, 1967; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Dr. Elyse Fleming, November 11, 1974; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 120)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and the Editorial Board of the History of Education, February 26, 1969; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and History of Education, February 15, 1968; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and History of Education, May 10, 1967; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and History of Education, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and History of Education, May 10, 1967; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and History of Education, February 15, 1968; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and the Editorial Board of H.E.Q., the Board of Directors of H.E.S., and Executive Officers of H.E.S.S., 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and the Editorial Board of H.E.Q., the Board of Directors of H.E.S., and the Executive Officers of the H.E.S, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and the Editorial Board of H.E.Q., the Board of Directors of the H.E.S., and Executive Officers of the H.E.S., February 26, 1969; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Edward Krug 1966, June 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Edward Krug 1966, June 24, 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and Ezri Atzmon, November 25, 1969; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and History of Education [1 of 2], May 10, 1967; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and History of Education [2 of 2], May 10, 1967; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and J.J. Chambliss, October 18, 1965; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and James Johnsonn, March- April 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and John Lankford and David Reimers, November- December 1968; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and John Sturm, January- February 1970; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and John Sturm and John Palmer, June 1969; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Mrs. Watson 1969, March 1969; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and Morey Fields, March 13, 1967; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Paul Nash, May 29, 1967; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Paul Nash 1966, undated; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Paul Nash 1968, June 12, 1968; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and the President and Board of Directors of H.E.S., October 1, 1969; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Axtell, January 20, 1970; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Beales, September 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Beales, October 6, 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Beales, January 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Beales, June 3, 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Beales 1966, February 28, 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Chambliss 1966, February 10, 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Church, January 20, 1970; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Cremin 1968, January 12, 1965; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Krug 1966, February 28, 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Nash 1966, January 12, 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence between Edward Krug and Professor Perkinson 1966, January 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Smith 1966, February 28, 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Stone, January 20, 1970; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Talbott, December 11, 1969; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence between Henry J. Perkinson and Professor Talbott, February 11, 1970; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and R. Freeman Butts, September 8, 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence Henry Perkinson and Robert Mason, September 20, 1965; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and the President and Board of Directors of the H.E.S., October 1, 1969; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and Samuel Levin, October 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and Vincent Lannie, October 30, 1967; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence between Henry Perkinson and William Drake, November 21, 1966; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence between Herman Baron and Mr. Perkinson 1968, October 2, 1968; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence between Herman Baron and Mr. Perkinsno 1969, July 25, 1969; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence between Hermino Vargas and Paul H. Mattingly, 1978; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence between History of Education Society and Jurgen Herbst, August 30, 1979; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence between H.E.S. Board of Directors H.E.S. Board of Directors and Carl Kaestle, November 20, 1980; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence between History of Education Society and Marvin Lazerson, 1982; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence between H.E.S. Committee and Sol Cohen, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence between History of Education Society Member and Wayne J. Urban, January 7, 1980; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence between H.E.S. Nominating Members Committee Members of History of Education: Professor Joan N. Burstyn and Carl Kaestle, November- December 1980; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence between Howard Webber and J.J. Chambliss, November 23, 1965; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence between Hy Kuritz to Paul Mattingly, September 25, 1981; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence between Hugh Hawkins and Paul Mattingly, January 1973- January 1974; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence between Ian Davey and Robin Berson, April 19-22, 1985; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence between Irvin Lehmann, William Mehrens, and Permissions Editor (H.E.S. Quarterly), August 21, 1969; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence between J. Donald, Joan Burstyn, David B. Tyack, and Carl Kaestle, November 25-26, 1980; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence between J. Donald Wilson and Paul Mattingly 1979, September- October 1979; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence between J.O.C. Phillips and Professor Mattingly 1979, May 23, 1979; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence between James C. Carper and Professor Carl F. Kaestle, April 10, 1981; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence between James C. Carper and Professor Carl F. Kaestle, February 9, 1981; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence between James C. McClelland and Dr. Berson 1979, November 26, 1979; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence between James F. Tent and Ms. Berson, September 3, 1981; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence between James Carper and Professor Robin Berson and Paul Mattingly 1980, Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence between James McLachlan and the MIT Press 1984, November 19, 1984; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence between James McLachlan and Professor Porter 1984, November 13, 1984; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence betweem James S. Hockley and Paul Mattingly, February- March 1974; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence between Jean LoBosco and Henry Perkinson- Agreement the School of Education New York University and the H.E.S., 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence between Jennings Wagoner and Carl Kaestle, May 29, 1985; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence between Jennings Wagoner and David Ment, 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence between Jennings L. Wagoner and Edward McClellan 1985, August 26, 1985; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence between Jennings Wagoner and Members of the Prize Committee, January 15, 1985; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence between Jennings L. Wagoner and Paul Mattingly 1979, March 5, 1979; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence between Jennings Wagoner and Paul Mattingly, June 18, 1984; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence between Jennings L. Wagoner and Professor Mattingly, 1973; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence between Jesse Lutz and Paul H. Mattingly, 1962-1973; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence between Jim Wallace and Carl Kaestle, November 6, 1980; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence between Jim Wallace and Dr. Mattingly 1980, March-April 1980; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence between Joan N. Burstyn and Carl Kaestle, February 19, 1981; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence between Joan Burstyn and David Ment, September 4, 1985; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence between Joan N. Burstyn and Robin Berson 1982, January 10, 1982; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence between Joe L. Green and Editor 1983, September 20, 1983; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence between Joe L. Perlmann and Ms. Berson 1981, May 24, 1981; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence between Joel R. and Robin Berson, July 22, 1983; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 87)